Guide to the Neill Family papers 1886-1964
Montana Historical Society
Neill Family papers
1886-1964
Montana Historical Society Archives
MC 248
Neill, John Selby Martin, 1860-1912
8 linear feet of shelf space
John Neill was a Helena, Montana, real estate man. Records (circa 1889-1930) concern his family real estate business and other investments and civic involvements. There are subgroups for John, his wife Margaret Neill, son George G.E. Neill, and for the Independent Investment Company, Independent Publishing Company, Lewis and Clark County Democratic Central Committee, Madison River Improvement Company, Montana Outdoor Advertising Company, Montana Properties Company, and Montana Rapid Transit Company.
John Neill was born in St. Paul, Minnesota, on March 25, 1860, the son of the Reverend Edward D. Neill and Nancy Hall Neill. When John was nine, President Ulysses S. Grant appointed his father consul to Ireland and the family moved to Dublin. After three years in Ireland, the family returned to Minneapolis, Minnesota. John graduated from Delaware College in 1881 and studied law at Columbian College in Washington, D.C. In 1883 he moved to Helena, Montana, where he became involved in real estate development. As a reward for his active work in re-electing President Grover Cleveland in 1892, Neill was appointed Surveyor General of Montana in 1895. In 1898, he became treasurer and manager of the Helena Independent newspaper and five years later purchased the paper. In 1909 Neill became a partner in the Montana Rapid Transit Company's ill-fated attempt to build an inter-urban railroad between Helena and Butte. In addition to his business and political activities, Neill was actively involved in numerous projects for Helena civic betterment, including attempts to expand the Mount Helena Park to include the forest land to the west, a plan to create the State Fairgrounds Boulevard along the current route of Henderson Avenue, development of Wesleyan University, and also work for the Democratic Party. In 1883 John Neill married Margaret G. Evans. The couple had one son, George G.E. Neill. John Neill died in Hot Springs, Arkansas, on March 22, 1912. Margaret G. Evans was born March 3, 1862, in Newark, Delaware, the daughter of George Gillespie Evans and Mary Black Evans. After the birth of her son George in 1884, she moved to Helena to join her husband. She became active in the civic life of Helena, serving as the first Democratic National Committeewoman from Montana, spearheading Helena's Red Cross drive during World War I, and working with several Presbyterian Church women's groups. After her husband's death, she became active in developing many of the real estate interests that she had inherited. She died March 6, 1951, in Helena. George G.E. Neill was born in Newark, Delaware, on October 30, 1884, and came to Helena with his mother shortly afterwards. He graduated from Princeton University in 1907. Many of the friendships he formed there continued throughout his life through his active participation in the Princeton alumni association. In 1908 he began working as bookkeeper for the Helena Independent and was promoted to treasurer two years later. After his father's death in 1912, George gave up management of the newspaper and became more active in real estate promotion. He was a partner with Lewis Penwell in the Capital Investment Company. In 1920 he was appointed Receiver of the Helena Land Office and served until 1923. He later formed the Montana Outdoor Advertising Company and the Montana Properties Company. George Neill was married in March 1952 to Martha Morrison who had a son, John Morrison, and a daughter, Mary Morrison Nolte. George G.E. Neill died in Helena on June 3, 1964.
Collection consists of personal and business papers of John S.M. Neill, his wife Margaret G. Neill, and son George G.E. Neill. There are several business subgroups. The John S.M. Neill Subgroup consists of eight series: Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence (1891-1912), both arranged chronologically; Miscellaneous Correspondence (1900, 1908), arranged chronologically; Financial Records (1889-1912), including a ledger, a journal, tax records, and other materials; Legal Documents (1886-1906), including documents of the Capital City Improvement Company and miscellaneous deeds and leases; Subject Files (1889-1912) concerning various real estate and mining properties, the Democratic Party, and the State Capitol site and building; Miscellany, including Helena real estate lot books, a personal memo book, and drawings for the State Fair Grounds Boulevard and other properties; and two scrapbooks of Clippings (1889-1890) concerning Helena real estate and politics. The John S.M. Neill Estate Subgroup consists of real estate assessment lists (1912) and a petition (1912) by the Collins Land Company to the City of Helena. The Margaret G. Neill Subgroup consists of eight series: General Correspondence (1905-1943) arranged chronologically; Court Papers consisting of a case (1939-1941) against Jacob P. Nordby; minor Financial Records (1895-1941); Legal Documents (1912, 1914); Speeches concerning her Red Cross work; Subject Files (1909-1928) concerning the World War I Liberty Loan drive and Helena real estate; Miscellany, including a minute book (1895-1898) for the First Presbyterian Church Helping Hand Society, and a financial journal (1914-1919) for the Presbyterian Church Ladies Aid Society; and Clippings (1918) concerning Red Cross war work. The George G.E. Neill Subgroup contains nine series: Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence (1911-1960) arranged chronologically; Miscellaneous Correspondence (1911-1952, undated); Court Papers (1919-1949); minor Financial Records (1908-1953); Legal Documents (1913-1940); Subject Files (1908-1922) concerning the Barnes-King Development Company and the State Fair Grounds; Miscellany, including drawings for various buildings, a list of patented mining claims in the Helena Mining District, and a list of property ownership in the vicinity of Holter Dam; and Clippings about the Gallatin County Development Association and Democratic politics. There are small personal subgroups for Elisha S. Clark and for George Evans. The Elisha S. Clark Subgroup consists of invoices, including his estate (1887-1896). The George Evans Subgroup consists of legal documents (1888-1892) from the Harriet B. Miles estate. The Independent Investment Company Subgroup records include: Incoming Correspondence (1914, 1918); minor Financial Records (1904-1928); Legal Documents (1904-1928), including an abstract of title for the Independent building; and a minute book (1906-1916). The Independent Publishing Company Subgroup records include: General Correspondence (1904-1926); Court Papers regarding a case (1899) involving Fred Whiteside; minor Financial Records (1906-1934); Legal Documents (1901-1917); a Subject File (1892-1907) concerning the state printing contract; and Miscellany (1913-1926, undated), including Cass Gilbert drawings for planned additions to the Independent's building. The Lewis and Clarke County Democratic Central Committee Subgroup consists of two poll books (undated) listing registered Democrats in each ward of Helena and each community in the county. Records in the Madison River Improvement Company Subgroup include General Correspondence (1910-1950); Financial Records consisting of tax records (1919-1937); and Miscellany (1909-1937, undated), including a deed (1920) for land along the Madison River and sketch maps. The Montana Outdoor Advertising Company Subgroup includes General Correspondence (1927-1961); Financial Records consisting of summaries (1952-1958); and Miscellany (1929, 1957), including lists of billboard locations and a charter for the Outdoor Advertising Association of Montana. Records in the Montana Properties Company Subgroup include General Correspondence (1917-1947); Court Papers (1939-1941) regarding a suit by the City of Helena; and Legal Documents consisting of deeds (1921, 1925). The Montana Rapid Transit Company Subgroup records include General Correspondence (1908-1921); Employment Records consisting of payrolls (1909); Financial Records, including financial summaries (1910), a ledger (1909-1922), transcripts of books (1909-1913), trial balances (1909-1921), and tax records (1909-1925); Legal Documents (1908-1940); Organizational Records, including record books (1909-1924), annual statements (1910-1922), and other materials; Printed Materials consisting of a brochure (circa 1909) about the company; and Miscellany, including drawings of the planned route of the railroad through Helena and East Helena.
Arranged by subgroup and series. Some material housed in Oversize Boxes, Manuscript Volumes, and Archives Map Case. See inventory below for more information.
Collection open for research.
Acquisition information available upon request.
Photographs, maps and artifacts transferred to the Photograph Archives, Library Map Collection, and Museum respectively. See box 15 folder 11 for listing of items transferred.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Neill, John Selby Martin, 1860-1912
Helena (Mont.)--buildings, structures, etc.; Helena (Mont.)--commerce--real estate; Helena (Mont.)--politics and government; Mount Helena (Mont.); Beaverhead National Forest (Mont.); Cliff Lake (Mont.); Wade Lake (Mont.)
Capitols; Street-railroads; World War, 1914-1918--war work--Montana
Logging; Montana
Detailed Description of the Collection
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection
- John Neill Papers
  - Biographical Material
    - Biographical information file (includes obituaries, biographical sketches, etc.), 1912-1996 (Box-folder 1 / 1)
- John Neill
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include T.E. Crutcher; Robert Valentine; T.H. Stevens; Charles Kaestner and Company; W.H. Webb; R.J. Sloan; "Reub"; W.C. Johnson; J.D. Tietjen; Frank L. Sizer; William A. Clark; Sam Toleman), 1891-1900 (Box-folder 1 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include William Scallon; Samuel T. Hauser; E.C. Day; Thomas H. Carter; John H. Farmer; Charles C. Wallin; Powell Black; John D. Ryan; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; William A. Clark), 1904-1906 (Box-folder 1 / 3)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Samuel T. Hauser; United States Reclamation Service; United States Corps of Engineers; Samuel G. Blythe; George G.E. Neill; John Barrett; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Carpenter, Day and Carpenter; Olaf Ussing; Thomas J. Walsh; Frank Lindsay; Philadephia Electric Company re work of Edward D. Neill; G.E. Gilliland), 1907 (Box-folder 1 / 4)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Barnes-King Development Company; G.E. Gilliland re Capital City Improvement Company dam across Missouri River; A.W. Martin; Cass Gilbert re remodelling of Independent Publishing Company building; George H. Carsley re new library building; J.P. Fister; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Samuel T. Hauser), 1908 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Cass Gilbert re Capitol renovation; Olaf Ussing; M.L. Hewett; H.M. Byllesby and Company; Otto E. Osthoff; W.E. Cullen Jr.; Collins Land Company; Union Bank and Trust Company; George L. Ramsey; Trowbridge and Niver Company; Chicago, Joliet and St. Louis Electric Railway Company; Samuel T. Hauser; G.E. Gilliland re history of Fort Harrison; J.E. Swindlehurst; G.H. Carsley re Helena Park plans; T.J. Walsh; E.C. Day; E.L. Trask), 1909-1910 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include William T. Pigott; T.J. Walsh; Union Bank and Trust Company; George L. Ramsey; M.H. Gerry Jr.; United Missouri River Power Company; John D. Ryan; William Allen Butler; Samuel T. Hauser; W.E. Cullen Jr.; D.C. Corbin; Three Forks Land Company; J.Q. Adams; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Cass Gilbert re Broadwater Hotel), 1911-1912 (Box-folder 1 / 7)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Letterpress book, 1894-1902 (Box-folder 2 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1895, 1905-1912 (Box-folder 2 / 2-5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - W.G. Eggleston to Philadelphia North American; unidentified writer to Scott R. Fair re pardon for James Harvey Whitton, 1900, 1908 (Box-folder 2 / 6)
  - Financial Records
    - Bank papers, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
    - Inventory of assets, undated (Box-folder 3 / 2)
    - Journal, 1889-1909 (Volume 1)
    - Ledger, 1889-1909 (Volume 2)
    - Life insurance assessments, 1888-1911 (Box-folder 3 / 3)
    - Taxes, 1889-1912 (Box-folder 3 / 4)
      RESTRICTED
    - Vouchers, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 3 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 3 / 6)
  - Legal Documents
    - Capital City Improvement Company, 1906 (Box-folder 3 / 7)
    - Miscellaneous (includes agreements, leases, mining claims, abstract of title), 1886-1904, undated (Box-folder 3 / 8)
  - Subject Files
    - Alexander Buchanan's real estate in Superior, Wisconsin, 1891-1902 (Box-folder 3 / 9)
    - Calendar Mining Company (Winston, Mont.), 1899-1900 (Box-folder 3 / 10)
    - Church and Elliott properties, 1902-1908 (Box-folder 3 / 11)
    - City Park Syndicate, 1889-1894 (Box-folder 3 / 12)
    - Democratic Party (includes list of county committeemen; minutes of Martin Maginnis vs. William A. Clark meeting), 1898-1912 (Box-folder 3 / 13)
    - "January", "February", "March", and "April" mining claims, 1896-1902 (Box-folder 3 / 14)
    - Madison River Canal, 1905 (Box-folder 3 / 15)
    - Missouri River Improvement Company; Capital City Improvement Company; United Missouri River Power Company, 1901-1922 (Box-folder 4 / 1)
    - Real estate: Helena, 1888-1908 (Box-folder 4 / 2)
    - Seymour mining claim, 1907 (Box-folder 4 / 3)
    - Soldiers' land claims (re R.G. Davies and Great Falls land), 1889-1890 (Box-folder 4 / 4)
    - State Capitol site and building (also includes list of property acquisitions in Northern Pacific Railroad Addition, 1868-1894) [letterpress copies], undated (Box-folder 4 / 5)
    - Stillwater mining claim, Jefferson County, 1892-1902 (Box-folder 4 / 6)
    - Victoria and Blue-Eyed Nellie mining claims, Jefferson County, 1891-1897 (Box-folder 4 / 7)
    - Violet Jane and Miljour mining claims, Lewis and Clark County (operated by B.N.J. Miljour), 1898-1906, 1926 (Box-folder 4 / 8-9)
  - Miscellany
    - Affidavit of M.N. Quentin re alleged political corruption by Helena Mayor F.J. Edwards, 1902 (Box-folder 4 / 10)
    - Army discharge of John S.M. Neill, 1882 (Box-folder 4 / 11)
    - Helena and Livingston Smelting and Refining Company stockholder list, 1897 (Box-folder 4 / 12)
    - Helena real estate lot books (arranged by addition), circa 1889 (Volume 3-4)
    - Memo book (includes diary entries, lists of Utica area residents with political affiliation, etc.), 1892 (Box-folder 4 / 13)
    - Plans and drawings (includes terracing at Central School, machinery at Lake Superior Carbide Works) [Oversize Box], undated (Oversizebox 16)
    - Plans and drawings (includes State Fair Grounds Boulevard) [Oversize: See Archives Map Case], 1910, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Subscriptions to unidentified enterprise (includes names of most prominent Helena businessmen), undated (Box-folder 4 / 14)
    - Writings of unidentified person(s) re railroads, politics, etc., 1896-1900, undated (Box-folder 4 / 15)
    - Miscellaneous (includes Gold Block and V Building bond offerings; architectural drawing for Helena depot; lists of companies), 1900, 1911, undated (Box-folder 4 / 16)
  - Clippings
    - Scrapbook (re Helena real estate, resources, Board of Trade, etc.), 1889-1890 (Box-folder 4 / 17)
    - Scrapbook (re Helena real estate, Sen. Thomas H. Carter, etc.), 1890 (Box-folder 5 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous (re Democratic politics, State Boulevard, Langhorne case, Thomas H. Carter involvement in Alaska scandal, Martin Maginnis, Nathaniel Pitt Langford, river navigation, etc.), 1902-1912 (Box-folder 5 / 2)
- John S.m. Neill Estate
  - Financial Records
    - Real estate assessment lists; miscellaneous, 1912 (Box-folder 5 / 3)
  - Legal Documents
    - Petition of Collins Land Company to City of Helena, 1912 (Box-folder 5 / 4)
- Margaret G. Neill
  - General Correspondence
    - Charles B. Evans, 1905 (Box-folder 6 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include T.J. Walsh; Democratic Party; Edith R. Battey; George G.E. Neill; Mary Gentry; Smithsonian Institution; Security Trust Company; Edward D. Neill), 1913-1943 (Box-folder 6 / 2)
  - Court Papers
    - Margaret G. Neill vs. Jacob P. Nordby, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 6 / 3)
  - Financial Records
    - Income distribution from George G. Evans Estate, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 6 / 4)
    - Taxes, 1905-1923 (Box-folder 6 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous (includes promissory notes, receipts, checkstubs, invoices, interest payments, Unemployment Compensation Commission forms), 1895-1941 (Box-folder 6 / 6)
  - Legal Documents
    - Miscellaneous (includes applications for city loans, loan agreements, mortgage), 1912, 1914 (Box-folder 6 / 7)
  - Speeches
    - Red Cross war work, circa 1918 (Box-folder 6 / 8)
  - Subject Files
    - Liberty Loan drive, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 6 / 9)
    - Real estate: Helena, 1909-1928 (Box-folder 6 / 10)
  - Miscellany
    - First Presbyterian Church Helping Hand Society record book (includes minutes, annual report, membership lists), 1895-1898 (Box-folder 6 / 11)
    - First Presbyterian Church Ladies Aid Society journal, 1914-1919 (Box-folder 6 / 12)
    - Will of Charles B. Evans, 1901 (Box-folder 6 / 13)
  - Clippings
    - Red Cross war work, 1918 (Box-folder 6 / 14)
- George G.e. Neill
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include William Allen Butler; John S.M. Neill; W.E. Cullen; Mercedes Fulenwider; T.J. Walsh; D.C. Corbin; S.V. Stewart; Lewis Penwell), 1911-1912 (Box-folder 7 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include W.E. Cullen; Lewis Penwell; Henry Breckenridge; E. D. Weed; D.C. Corbin; Newark Trust and Safe Deposit Company; Charles B. Evans; E.C. Day), 1913 (Box-folder 7 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include T.J. Walsh; Dickenson and Gillespie Inc.; J.K. Toole; Max Hebgen; David Hilger; W.E. Cullen; Tom Stout; John M. Evans; E.L Trask; M.H. Gerry Jr.; George L. Ramsey; J.Q. Adams; Petterson, Dinsmore and Company; David G. Browne; Henry Neill; D.C. Corbin; Newark Trust and Safe Deposit Company; Charles B. Evans), 1914 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include E.L. Trask; T.J. Walsh; George B. Hopkins; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; J.Q. Adams; R.H. Veitch; D.C. Corbin; E.D. Weed; W.E. Cullen; Edward D. Neill, Jr.), 1915 (Box-folder 7 / 4)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include E.L. Trask; George L. Ramsey; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Lewis Penwell; E.D. Weed; T.O. Hammond; Capital Investment Company; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Henry Neill; Edward D. Neill Jr.; H.A. Frank; J.Q. Adams; D.C. Corbin; Charles W. Gamer), 1916 (Box-folder 7 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Edward D. Neill Jr.; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Capital Investment Company; Montana Properties Company; J.Q. Adams; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; D.C. Corbin; E.L. Trask; Board of Fire Underwriters; E.D. Weed; T.A. Harding; N.P. Dodge and Company), 1917 (Box-folder 7 / 6)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include J.Q. Adams; E.D. Weed; N.P. Dodge and Company; Jack L. Carter; L.O. Evans; L.B. Blankman, Marcus Daly Estate; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; Eugene B. Milburn, Montana Wholesale Land Company; Capital Investment Company; Montana Properties Company; R.H. Fletcher; A.A. Hofman; T.B. Weir; John Power), 1918 (Box-folder 7 / 7)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include J.Q. Adams; N.P. Dodge and Company; W.M. Nevitt; United States Railroad Administration; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; F.M. Kerr; Jack Fisk; endorsements of R.H. Fletcher for Surveyor General; Montana Wesleyan College), 1919 (Box-folder 7 / 8)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include M.H. Gerry Jr.; Montana Rapid Transit Company; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; Montana Properties Company; Barnes-King Development Company; the Banking Corporation of Montana; Charles B. Evans; Jack Fisk; Continental Oil Company; J.J. O'Neill; A.E. Spriggs; United States Land Office; E.D. Weed; Capital Investment Company), 1920 (Box-folder 7 / 9)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include M.H. Gerry Jr.; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; Charles B. Evans; Continental Oil Company; J.J. O'Neill; Helena Fuel Company; Donald Livestock Company; George L. Ramsey), 1921 (Box-folder 7 / 10)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Charles B. Evans; Hugh R. Wells; George L. Ramsey; B.H. Ellis; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; "Bunny"; Jeremiah Collins; Edward D. Neill, Jr.; N.P. Dodge and Company; George F. Charlesworth), 1922-1923 (Box-folder 7 / 11)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Edward D. Neill, Jr.; George F. Charlesworth; H.L. "Herb" Brooks; Margaret G. Neill; George L. Ramsey; Receiver for Banking Corporation of Montana; W.M. "Mudge" Brooks; Charles B. Evans; N.P. Dodge and Company), 1924 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include John M. Evans; Norton P. Otis; H.L. "Herb" Brooks; Charles B. Evans; Gene Holden; Ed Wishon; William L. Creden; Dickinson and Gillespie, Inc.; M.H. Gerry Jr.; Warren H. Colson; Ed Wishon; Ruth M. Veitch; Gans and Klein Investment Company; Earl Williams), 1925 (Box-folder 7 / 13)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Bob Veitch; John M. Evans; S.P. Burr; Ray Church; Nellie McDonald; Mabel Platt; Charles B. Evans; Thomas Metcalf; Blanche Small; George L. Ramsey; Paige-Detroit Motor Car Company; Phil G. Cole; Joseph M. Dixon; T.J. Walsh), 1926 (Box-folder 7 / 14)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include United States Veterans Bureau re G.C. Elliott; John M. Evans; Charles B. Evans; G.C. Elliott; Mabel Platt; E.T. Dusenbury; John A. Mathews; George J. Willock; Josiah Blackburn), 1927 (Box-folder 7 / 15)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Harral S. Tenney; G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; Helena and Livingston Smelting and Reduction Company; John M. Evans; Charles B. Evans; Josiah Blackburn; Gordon S. Rentschler), 1928 (Box-folder 7 / 16)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; John G. Brown; C.W. Merrilies), 1929 (Box-folder 7 / 17)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; Philip G. Cole; Evinrude Division of Outboard Motors Corporation; Walter H. Wheeler; C.A. Spaulding), 1930 (Box-folder 8 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; George W. McLean; Evinrude Division of Outboard Motors Corporation; General Surety Company of Montana; C.A. Spaulding), 1931 (Box-folder 8 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; Caille Motor Company; Beaverhead National Forest Jess E. Pierman; Byron Felton; W.M. "Mudge" Brooks; Mabel Platt; Milton S. Gunn; John M. Evans; Edward D. Neill), 1932 (Box-folder 8 / 3)
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include G.C. Elliott; Bob Veitch; Charles E. Pew; Beaverhead National Forest; Hotel Investment Company; Jess E. Pierman; Lena Evans; Byron Felton; John H. Crone; Newark Trust Company; Philip G. Cole), 1933 (Box-folder 8 / 4)